# **Emmanuel Uchenna**

**Experienced Frontend Developer** 



eunithelp@gmail.com ■

(+234) (0) 811-0863-115

Ebonyi, Nigeria 🖊

https://eunit.me %

https://github.com/eunit99 🛂

https://linkedin.com/in/eunit99 in

## **CAREER PROFILE**

Passionate frontend developer with 4+ years developing responsive, intuitive frontend solutions. I am looking to obtain a frontend developer role where my responsive UI design skills, my knowledge in a wide variety of software, programming languages will contribute to building high performing, accessible and scalable web applications.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### frontend developer

BACF Inc.

Jan. 2021 - Present

Remote

#### **Accomplishments / Tasks**

- Converted UI mock-ups to functional, responsive website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery.
- Worked with the product and tech team to solve daily business problems.
- Charged with the responsibility of developing responsive, beautiful, and pixel-perfect websites.

### frontend developer

### Credipple

Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Remote

### **Accomplishments / Tasks**

- Converted UI mock-ups to functional, responsive website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery.
- Worked with a team to build the home and about pages
- Charged with the responsibility of developing responsive user interfaces.

## frontend developer

#### LabsAl

Mar. 2020 - May 2020

Remote

### **Accomplishments / Tasks**

- Built responsive conversational user interfaces for chatbots
- Built Ella bot, hapBot, and also contributed to the development of Bo – an onboarding chatbot.

### INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

Single Page App Development Storybook

Responsive Web Development Accessibility

GIT / Version Control Component Design

Web Scrapping User Interface Design

## **SKILLS**

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript ReactJS

jQuery SASS/SCSS Styled Components

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Frontend development (2020 - 2021) Udemy.com

# **EDUCATION**

### B.Sc. Anatomy

Alex Ekwueme Federal University, Ebonyi State.

# **LANGUAGES**

#### English

**Full Professional Proficiency** 

#### French

**Bilingual Proficiency**